Lamborghini: The Man Behind the Legend is a drama,
history film directed by Bobby Moresco.
Follow the launch of Lamborghini’s career as a manufacturer of tractors, a creator of military vehicles during World War II, and the
designer of Lamborghini cars, which he launched in 1963 as the high-end sports car company Automobili Lamborghini.
Ferruccio Lamborghini, played by Frank Grillo.
Young Ferruccio Lamborghini, played by Romano Reggiani.
Enzo Ferrari, played by Gabriel Byrne.
Matteo, played by Matteo Leoni.
Clelia Monti, played by Hannah van der Westhuysen.
Anita Borgatti, played by Mira Sorvino.
Lamborghini: The Man Behind the Legend is a 2022 American biographical drama film written and directed by
Robert Moresco and starring Frank Grillo as Italian entrepreneur Ferruccio Lamborghini.
It was released in select theaters in the United States on November
18, 2022 by Lionsgate, and was panned by critics.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
biography, historical, auto industry, luxury car.
The tone is emotional.